[Music]
[音乐]
我的名字叫邓肯·伯明翰
my name is Duncan Birmingham my
专业是教授弹出式设计，
这是一系列的第一个
my name is Duncan Birmingham my
speciality is teaching pop-up design and
教程向您展示如何使自己变得高度
复杂的弹出窗口非常简单，所以我
speciality is teaching pop-up design and
this is the first in a series of
首先要经历
该材料的基本材料
this is the first in a series of
tutorials showing you how to make highly
您需要的是胶水剪刀和卡片
我推荐的卡类型是160 GSM
tutorials showing you how to make highly
complex pop-ups very easy way so I'm
可以使用更重的卡180 gsm到220
您也可以使用重型墨盒
complex pop-ups very easy way so I'm
going to start by just running through
纸张真的取决于大小
您正在制作的弹出窗口中的
going to start by just running through
the materials the basic materials that
这些教程将使用影印本
最好的胶水是160 GSM的卡
the materials the basic materials that
you need are glue scissors and card the
溶剂型粘合剂水基工程
好的，但是它往往会使卡
you need are glue scissors and card the
type of card I recommend is 160 GSM you
扣，它脱落得更慢，所以
用棍子工作要困难得多
type of card I recommend is 160 GSM you
can use heavier card 180 gsm up to 220
胶水还可以，而且很好干净
和易于使用，但它们往往会破解
can use heavier card 180 gsm up to 220
you can also use heavy-duty cartridge
所以过了一会儿，你的弹出窗口
会分解其他材料
you can also use heavy-duty cartridge
paper really it all depends on the size
在这些第一个教程中您将不需要
但在后来的更多
paper really it all depends on the size
of the pop-up that you're making but for
复杂
你真的需要我这种类型的工艺刀
of the pop-up that you're making but for
these tutorials will be using photocopy
像这种带有可扩展按扣的类型
刀片外，您需要金属尺子
these tutorials will be using photocopy
cards which is 160 GSM the best glue is
尺子好，你可以切长直
指南针对着边缘的线
cards which is 160 GSM the best glue is
solvent based adhesive water base works
画圈，再一次
您只需要一些机制
solvent based adhesive water base works
okay but it tends to make the card
对于，但这只是一个方便的工具
您的工具箱也可以用于
okay but it tends to make the card
buckle and it goes off more slowly so
用测量笔记测量
从一个模型转移长度
buckle and it goes off more slowly so
it's much harder to work with stick
给另一个量角器并设置平方
用于测量角度和圆珠笔
it's much harder to work with stick
glues are okay they're nice and clean
没有墨水，因此在弹出式窗口中得分很高
得分对于获得
glues are okay they're nice and clean
and easy to use but they tend to crack
漂亮干净的折叠，你给它打了个圆珠
没有墨水的钢笔倾向于
and easy to use but they tend to crack
and so after a while yeah your pop-ups
压缩梳理机中的纤维
比削减他们，是的，我真的
and so after a while yeah your pop-ups
will fall apart the other materials that
推荐没有墨水的圆珠笔
当然是的
will fall apart the other materials that
you won't need in these first tutorials
你永远都知道的铅笔和橡胶
现在我想减少一些方便的材料
you won't need in these first tutorials
but in the later ones which are more
从最基础的
弹出窗口最基本的弹出窗口
but in the later ones which are more
complex
我们将只使用一小部分
像这样的卡片在中间全部折叠
complex
you need a craft knife the type I really
这些早期的教程绝对有
不能衡量所有事情只是通过
you need a craft knife the type I really
like is this type with a extendable snap
眼睛，所以你可以切一小块
眼睛将卡片对折
like is this type with a extendable snap
off blade you'll need a ruler a metal
在弹出窗口中非常重要，因此
你越折越越甜
off blade you'll need a ruler a metal
ruler is good you can cut long straight
小动作，我一直想起褶皱
就像他们像铰链和折痕一样
ruler is good you can cut long straight
lines against the edge a compass for
折叠完全就像给
铰链，以便您拿起这张卡片
lines against the edge a compass for
drawing circles with and again there's
从折叠中切成一个
边缘，然后将其弯曲
drawing circles with and again there's
only a few mechanisms that you need this
我们像这样弯腰
看起来像将它折叠起来
only a few mechanisms that you need this
for but it's just a handy tool to have
打开它并通过它推动
这种类型最基本的弹出式窗口是
for but it's just a handy tool to have
your tool box you can also use it for
收敛的折痕所以所有这四个
折痕折痕折痕
your tool box you can also use it for
measuring with measuring notes
在中间，每边两个
所有人都汇聚在同一点
measuring with measuring notes
transferring lengths from one one model
弹出窗口的类型是平行折痕，所以我们
再拿一张卡片对折
transferring lengths from one one model
to another a protractor and set square
像往常一样彻底
如果时间再次减少两次，这是
to another a protractor and set square
for measuring angles and a ballpoint pen
我从中切入的折叠边缘
甚至不需要的折叠边缘
for measuring angles and a ballpoint pen
without any ink so scoring on big pop up
用剪刀就可以撕开
线条不一定要笔直
without any ink so scoring on big pop up
scoring can be really important to get a
可以将他们摇晃地锯齿
角度再随便折吧
scoring can be really important to get a
nice clean fold you score it a ballpoint
返回，所以您得到此形状将其折回
对自己增强折痕打开它
nice clean fold you score it a ballpoint
pen with no ink it tends to it just
向上推动它，以便获得一种
踩这两个这两件
pen with no ink it tends to it just
compresses the fibers in the card rather
展示基本的基础
所有弹出窗口的原则所有弹出窗口
compresses the fibers in the card rather
than cutting them so yeah I really
所有折痕都在同一时间相遇
点他们正在收敛折痕
than cutting them so yeah I really
recommend ballpoint pen without any ink
在脊椎的同一点开会
其他类型的平行折痕
recommend ballpoint pen without any ink
and of course yeah
所有折痕都平行于
脊椎，这是两个基础
and of course yeah
pencil and rubber you know just always
所有弹出窗口中的原则，所以这种类型
适当机制的称为计数器
pencil and rubber you know just always
handy less materials now I'd like to
折叠，这是我做的一个例子
和一些学校的孩子在一起，所以这是
handy less materials now I'd like to
start with the most elementary of
柜台折叠它是这种类型的
收敛的折痕
start with the most elementary of
pop-ups the most elementary pop-ups
变成一张脸，然后粘在一个
背景，这真的很基本
pop-ups the most elementary pop-ups
we're just going to use a small piece of
简单的东西有一本书有一些
在这是这是晚餐时间
we're just going to use a small piece of
card like this fold it in the middle all
冠军科夫斯基看第一场
这是这些V形汇合中的一种
card like this fold it in the middle all
these early tutorials there's absolutely
折痕融合折痕弹出窗口，我们可以
还要看看这个的最后传播
these early tutorials there's absolutely
no measuring everything is just done by
书，这是这下颚
这条鲨鱼正在收敛，这是
no measuring everything is just done by
eye so you can just cut a small piece of
V形折叠和顶部抽屉
鲨鱼是您永远可以看到的平行褶皱
eye so you can just cut a small piece of
card by eyes fold it in half folds are
告诉平行褶皱，如果您看着
书本就可以往下看
card by eyes fold it in half folds are
really important in pop-ups so the more
您会看到，尽管所有
折痕与此类型的平行
really important in pop-ups so the more
you the more you fold it the most sweet
机制可以应用于任何折叠
任何弹出式窗口，因此您可以使用此类型
you the more you fold it the most sweet
little moves its I always think of folds
机制的一部分
雕刻
little moves its I always think of folds
as like they're like hinges and creasing
雕塑或可以将其用作
肌肉举起更大的一块
as like they're like hinges and creasing
the fold thoroughly is like greasing the
卡，所以如果我们看这本书和这个
是海伦轰炸机在丛林时代，
the fold thoroughly is like greasing the
hinge so you take this piece of cards we
是反折的一个例子
用于剥落实际弹出窗口
hinge so you take this piece of cards we
cut into it just one cut from the folded
这是反折
当书打开时关闭，您可以看到
cut into it just one cut from the folded
edge and then just bend that over so
它移动了，但这全是由
一张平的卡你实际上可以
edge and then just bend that over so
we're bending that over like this so it
关闭书，然后打开和关闭
像这样，这是反折
we're bending that over like this so it
looks like that fold it back on itself
被用作雕塑的一部分
设计这本书的机器人
open it up and push that through this is
冠军Kowski在这个弹出式传播中
这些柜台折痕他用过这种类型
open it up and push that through this is
the most elementary pop-up this type is
的折痕计数器折叠这些
是移动大块的肌肉，所以
the most elementary pop-up this type is
converging creases so all the all four
这是平行折叠，然后在这里
每一面都有这些小柜台
converging creases so all the all four
creases the spine folds the spoke fold
用来作为肌肉的褶皱
抬起这两个小机器人，这样
creases the spine folds the spoke fold
in the middle and the two on each side
该页面打开和关闭，您可以看到
肌肉的反折
in the middle and the two on each side
all converge at the same point the other
移动这两个两个小型机器人，但是
这些基本的弹出式窗口
all converge at the same point the other
type of pop-up is parallel creases so we
页面平坦时弹出窗口
是平坦的，实际上不是真的
type of pop-up is parallel creases so we
take another card fold it in half fold
弹出窗口，它们更像是你的东西
可以添加到弹出窗口，所以我将展示
take another card fold it in half fold
it thoroughly as usual
您如何制作两个弹出窗口
收敛折痕平行折痕
it thoroughly as usual
if time make two cuts again this is the
有三个校长三个
适用于所有人的重要原则
if time make two cuts again this is the
folded edge I'm cutting in from the
弹出第一个是，每个
弹出窗口必须跨越厨房，所以这是一个
folded edge I'm cutting in from the
folded edge you don't even actually need
我们将它折成两半
眼睛真的折皱了
folded edge you don't even actually need
to use scissors you can actually tear it
回到自身折痕这是
你的底片是厨房
to use scissors you can actually tear it
the lines don't have to be straight they
是厨房的开口，将提供动力
弹出窗口，我将制作一块
the lines don't have to be straight they
can be they can be Wiggly jagged at an
弹出窗口
所以再做一次，一切都是
can be they can be Wiggly jagged at an
angle whatever you like again fold it
用眼睛做，你只需要切
将卡片对折成半折
angle whatever you like again fold it
back so you get this shape fold it back
真的很彻底，第二
原则是弹出窗口必须
back so you get this shape fold it back
on itself to enhance the creases open it
厨房两侧的平衡
所以弹出式数学Panigale他们必须
on itself to enhance the creases open it
up push it through so you get a kind of
粘在厨房的两侧
然后他们必须在每一侧保持平衡
up push it through so you get a kind of
step these two these two pieces
的沟壑，所以在这种情况下，我们
产生V折的收敛折痕
step these two these two pieces
demonstrate the basic underlying
带有v形折叠的角度
平衡，这是我们的弹出窗口
demonstrate the basic underlying
principles of all pop ups all pop ups
将标签折叠到底部
这样做会粘到页面上
principles of all pop ups all pop ups
either all the creases meet at the same
我们将两个角度
弹出窗口的每一侧都在同一位置
either all the creases meet at the same
points they're converging creases
他们都是九十度
再次加强那些褶皱
points they're converging creases
meeting at the same point on the spine
我们到了弹出窗口的角度
现在要保持平衡
meeting at the same point on the spine
the other type of parallel creases so
页面和底座上的两个角度
我们必须保持平衡，以便获得胶水
the other type of parallel creases so
all the creases are parallel to the
我用胶水的秘密是把胶水
在一侧，然后我总是
all the creases are parallel to the
spine and these are the two underlying
用我的小手指我用我的小手指
手指，以便我可以涂胶
spine and these are the two underlying
principles in all pop ups so this type
真的很均匀但是我的手指仍然
dextra，这样我就可以处理其他事情了
principles in all pop ups so this type
of proper mechanism is called counter
没有他们被卡住，这是真的
重要的是胶水一直上升到
of proper mechanism is called counter
folds and here's an example that I did
折痕弹出折痕是
胶水真的很重要
folds and here's an example that I did
with some school kids and so this is
增加所有测量到
折痕，所以这里我们去中央折痕
with some school kids and so this is
counter folds it's it's this type with
与沟壑和棍子对齐
那面朝下，现在你把整个
counter folds it's it's this type with
converging creases and it's made made
件关闭，在另一侧放胶
再次涂抹胶水直到折痕
converging creases and it's made made
into a face and it's just glued on to a
关好底座，然后按一下
第一个弹出窗口，因此在这种情况下，每个
into a face and it's just glued on to a
background so this is really basic
弹出跨越一个沟壑，然后
第二个原则是每个弹出窗口
background so this is really basic
simple stuff there is a book with some
沟渠两侧的失衡
有折痕的V形折叠
simple stuff there is a book with some
in it this is this is dinner time by
在同一点收敛
是平衡的角度，所以角度
in it this is this is dinner time by
champion Kowski look at the first spread
在这两个底座上都是一样大小
弹出的角度都是
champion Kowski look at the first spread
and it's one of these v-folds converging
相同的大小，所以如果我们称这个为a和this
B我们一侧有加号B
and it's one of these v-folds converging
crease converging creases pop-ups we can
另一边有加号B，所以
角度平衡，这是基本的V形折叠
crease converging creases pop-ups we can
also look at the last spread in this
[音乐]
这些有五种配置
also look at the last spread in this
book and here it is this bottom jaw of
文件夹，所以我将向您展示
其他五个，所以这是类型
book and here it is this bottom jaw of
this shark is converging creases this is
我们只是使这是正确的角度
v折叠弹出窗口上的角度为
this shark is converging creases this is
the V fold and the top drawer of the
两者都是90度这是锐角
v折叠它们所在的弹出窗口上的角度
the V fold and the top drawer of the
shark is a parallel fold you can always
仍然是相同的，但角度是
两者都小于90度
shark is a parallel fold you can always
tell parallel folds if you look at the
尖的v形褶皱，这是一个变化
在这个锐角上，但在这种情况下
tell parallel folds if you look at the
book end on you can look down the spine
更极端的是，这是
钝角默认为
book end on you can look down the spine
and you can see that although all the
弹出式窗口上都超过90
他们每个人的度数仍然相同
and you can see that although all the
creases are parallel this type of
侧面和底座上的角度
双方仍然一样
creases are parallel this type of
mechanism can be applied to any folds in
你有平衡，然后这就是
最后最吸引人的
mechanism can be applied to any folds in
any pop-up and so you can use this type
v形折叠真的是不对称的
V形折叠，因此
any pop-up and so you can use this type
of mechanism as actual part of the
弹出窗口是不同的，并且角度
基础不同，你有四个
of mechanism as actual part of the
sculpting of the
不同的角度，但在
在一侧的基础上加上在
sculpting of the
the sculpture or it can be used as just
弹出窗口等于
另一边加上角度
the sculpture or it can be used as just
the muscle to raise a larger piece of
弹出窗口，因此您仍然可以保持平衡
虽然所有四个角度都不一样
the muscle to raise a larger piece of
card so if we look at this book and this
[音乐]
现在我将弹出一个
card so if we look at this book and this
is jungle days by Helen bomber and this
平行折叠采取另一种基础，
这是一个弹出的片段，所以这是
is jungle days by Helen bomber and this
is an example of a counter fold being
平行折叠
所以在这种情况下，我们在
is an example of a counter fold being
used to scalp the actual pop-up so this
当你做的时候你的外边缘
制作粘贴标签，他们永远都不会
used to scalp the actual pop-up so this
here this is the counter fold as the
小于半英寸或一厘米
因为弹出窗口往往会产生
here this is the counter fold as the
book closes as it opens you can see how
标签上的压力很大，所以您
需要他们相当广泛才能接受
book closes as it opens you can see how
it moves and yet this is all made from
打开和关闭的压力，所以这是
将成为平行折叠，而你
it moves and yet this is all made from
one flat piece of card you can actually
真的可以和你一起玩
可以使它在页面上真正宽，或者
one flat piece of card you can actually
close the book and just open and close
你可以把它弄得很近我倾向于
实际切断了胶合的角落
close the book and just open and close
it like that so this is the counter fold
标签，我只是想当他们在
尖锐程度会降低
it like that so this is the counter fold
being used as part of the sculpture of
不管是否
他们在里面是这样还是
being used as part of the sculpture of
the design this book this is robot by
他们在外面这样你可以吗
知道标签的位置
the design this book this is robot by
champion Kowski in this pop-up spread
无关紧要的唯一事情
重要的是折痕的位置，所以
champion Kowski in this pop-up spread
these counter folds he's used these type
这是把它对折
然后折叠选项卡
these counter folds he's used these type
of converging crease counter folds these
平衡弹出框的长度
双方都是一样的，所以我们再次
of converging crease counter folds these
are the muscles to move larger pieces so
将胶水放在一侧上
一直打，直到我皱起来
are the muscles to move larger pieces so
this is a parallel fold and then here on
这些标签会在
里面，所以我们将其粘在那里
this is a parallel fold and then here on
each side you've got these small counter
折痕平行于中央沟
然后将整张纸折叠起来，放上胶水
each side you've got these small counter
folds that are used to as the muscle to
在另一个选项卡上将其涂抹到边缘
并关闭底座，以便找到它
folds that are used to as the muscle to
lift these two little robots and so as
自然的粘贴位置，所以这是一个
这是平行折叠，这是一个
lift these two little robots and so as
the page opens and closes you can see
对称平行折叠有三个
各种各样的平行褶皱是这个
the page opens and closes you can see
the counter folds that muscles are
是对称相等的平行折叠
双方都一样长
the counter folds that muscles are
moving those two two small robots but
在相同的弹出窗口上
从它粘到的距离
moving those two two small robots but
this type of pop-up these elementary
脊椎是一样的，所以在左边
在基地上有一小段时间
this type of pop-up these elementary
pop-ups when the page is flat the pop-up
在您右边的弹出窗口中
在底座上有一点点
pop-ups when the page is flat the pop-up
is flat and they're not actually true
在弹出窗口中，这是第二个
平行折叠的类型是
is flat and they're not actually true
pop-ups they're more like something you
平行四边形，你这样看
您可以在左侧的一侧看到
pop-ups they're more like something you
can add to pop-ups so I'm going to show
弹出窗口的长度很短
他们在基础上很长
can add to pop-ups so I'm going to show
you how to make two pop-ups one
右边的长度很短
弹出窗口的底部和较长的长度
you how to make two pop-ups one
converging creases one parallel creases
再次，您已经平衡了长度
平衡，最后一个是
there are three principals three
这是不对称的平行折叠
四个长度都不同，所以
there are three principals three
important principles that apply to all
离开时，您在
基地和短的弹出窗口
important principles that apply to all
pop-ups the first one is that every
右边的那一点
在弹出窗口上停留很长时间
pop-ups the first one is that every
pop-up must span a galley so this is a
所以当整个事情结束时，您可以看到
从脊椎褶皱到领先
pop-up must span a galley so this is a
base sheet we fold it in half do it by
领先的褶皱双方是相同的
弹出式窗口在V形折叠上处于平衡状态
base sheet we fold it in half do it by
eye crease it really thoroughly fold it
平行折叠处平衡的角度
这是平衡的长度，
eye crease it really thoroughly fold it
back on itself crease it again this is
第三
第三个原则是每个弹出窗口
back on itself crease it again this is
your base sheet this is the galley
创造沟壑，所以第一个原则
每次弹出我的扳手时，
your base sheet this is the galley
it's the galley opening that will power
第一沟是脊柱褶皱
原则上每个弹出窗口必须保持平衡
it's the galley opening that will power
the pop-up I'll take a piece to make the
每个部位V形折弯
平衡的平行褶皱就是长度
the pop-up I'll take a piece to make the
pop-ups with
平衡，然后是第三原则
是每个弹出窗口都会创建沟渠，
so do it again everything everything is
您可以将弹出窗口粘贴到这些沟渠中
所以这是一条平行折叠的沟
so do it again everything everything is
done by eye you just cut the piece of
可以像这样坚持下去
可以像这样坚持这个
done by eye you just cut the piece of
card in half fold it in half crease it
然后再在V形折叠上
你有这些可以粘的沟壑
card in half fold it in half crease it
really thoroughly and the second
页面关闭时将其放入背面
该弹出窗口将关闭，或者您也
really thoroughly and the second
principle is that pop-ups must must
有一个沟壑，你可以贴在那里
可以将弹出窗口粘贴到您的沟渠中
principle is that pop-ups must must
balance on each side of the galleys
可以将它贴在您喜欢的任何高度
我有一个例子的方式是这样的
balance on each side of the galleys
so pop-ups maths Panigale they must
是一个V形折叠，蓝色是
V形折叠
so pop-ups maths Panigale they must
stick down to both sides of the galley
并弹出堆栈这是一个
平行的折痕卡在这条沟里
stick down to both sides of the galley
and then they must balance on each side
这是收敛的折痕或卡在
这些都是不同的形式
and then they must balance on each side
of the gully so in this case we're
的弹出窗口卡在不同的窗口中
沟渠在这里，你有一个例子
of the gully so in this case we're
making a converging crease of V folds so
像这样的柜台折
这是一个很大的反折
making a converging crease of V folds so
with v-folds it's the angles that
同样的原则适用于这件作品
弹出窗口，您可以使用三种方式
with v-folds it's the angles that
balance so here's the pop-up piece we're
基地基地可以是一个
从中弹出的基础可以
balance so here's the pop-up piece we're
folding the tabs onto the bottom which
是弹出窗口出现的背景
从它前进，也可以是一个基地和一个
folding the tabs onto the bottom which
will glue to the page by doing it this
背景并且弹出窗口卡住了
进软糖，所以我想要的第一个
will glue to the page by doing it this
way we've made the two the two angles on
告诉你，这就是克里斯托弗
哥伦布再见subasta，这是一个弹出窗口
way we've made the two the two angles on
each side of the pop-up at the same in
50年代
这是使用这是使用基地作为
each side of the pop-up at the same in
this case they're both ninety degrees
以a为基础，弹出窗口从
它
again reinforce those those folds so
有，这是如果你实际上
从顶部看它，你会发现它是
again reinforce those those folds so
we've got there the angles on the pop-up
基于v-fold，尽管它在哪里
将所有折痕粘贴到页面上
we've got there the angles on the pop-up
a balancing now we've got to stick it to
在同一点收敛，所以这是
这是一个使用base作为
a balancing now we've got to stick it to
the page and the two angles on the base
从中弹出的基础
第二种方法可以使用
the page and the two angles on the base
we've got to balance so we get the glue
基地是以基地为背景的
弹出窗口随之而来
we've got to balance so we get the glue
my secret with glue is to put the glue
这是哭鲨的小鱼
因此，如果我们打开这个，这就是
my secret with glue is to put the glue
on on just on one side and then I always
基础作为背景，所以您已经
从它弹出的弹出窗口
on on just on one side and then I always
use my little finger I use my little
而且在这种情况下，两个都减半
基于V折的设计
use my little finger I use my little
finger so that I can spread the glue
他们在我看来像是对称的
v形折叠，所以两个角度都弹出
finger so that I can spread the glue
really evenly but my fingers remain
弹出窗口的每一侧都不同，因此
这是使用弹出窗口作为
really evenly but my fingers remain
dextra so I can handle other things and
背景，第三种是
另一个电容器又是
dextra so I can handle other things and
without them getting stuck it's really
50年代是基础和背景
那是我想做的最后一件事
without them getting stuck it's really
important that the glue goes right up to
谈论真正的技术，然后
我想说的最后一件事是
important that the glue goes right up to
the crease the crease in pop up is
所有所有弹出窗口都使用以下组合
机制，所以我有一些例子
the crease the crease in pop up is
really important the glue goes to the
这是我做的时候这是这
V折三折，然后这个V
really important the glue goes to the
crease all measuring is done to the
前面的折叠正在加注
这只狗和那只狗是由一只
crease all measuring is done to the
crease so here we go the central crease
整个平行四边形系列
是这个设计的组合
crease so here we go the central crease
is lined up with the gully and stick
V折和
平行四边形，然后这是一个
is lined up with the gully and stick
that side down now you fold the whole
是一个非常早期的弹出窗口
从30年代开始
that side down now you fold the whole
piece shut put glue on the other side
叫做Baccano系列，这是
15号，我认为他们大约30岁，
again smear the glue up to the crease
设计师是一个叫路易莎的家伙
罗恩，所以这是这是这是一个
shut the base press it well and here's
再次弹出，您可以看到基本的
部分
shut the base press it well and here's
the first pop-up so in this case every
是V型折叠，而V型折叠正在上升
平行四边形提高了其他
the first pop-up so in this case every
pop out spans a gully and then the
图片，所以如果你这样看
在你周围，你会发现其他
pop out spans a gully and then the
second principle is every pop-up
平行四边形的图像由
折叠
second principle is every pop-up
misbalance on each side of the gully
然后这是一个更现代的
是David Pellom Appleby的造型，
misbalance on each side of the gully
with v-folds where the crease is all
这是同一件事，我们在这里
有Appleby的形状吗？
with v-folds where the crease is all
converge at the same point
V型折叠又是一个可爱的角度V型折叠
它提高了平行四边形，所以你看起来
converge at the same point
it's the angles at balance so the angles
这样就可以看到
它是V形折叠产生的平行四边形
it's the angles at balance so the angles
on the base here are both the same size
还有另外一个是这个
我最喜欢的这是Chuck Murphy
on the base here are both the same size
the angles on the pop up are both the
黑猫，白猫，在这种情况下
你有这个，这是非常不寻常的
the angles on the pop up are both the
same size so if we call this a and this
建设这是v折的
盒是V型折叠，实际上是一个
same size so if we call this a and this
B we've got a plus B on one side we've
是盒子后面的平行四边形
但这是盒子的前半部分
B we've got a plus B on one side we've
got a plus B on the other side so the
V形褶皱提高了整体
你这样看的结构
got a plus B on the other side so the
angles balanced this is the basic v-fold
你可以看到梯子和
其他一切都是平行折叠
angles balanced this is the basic v-fold
[Music]
这是所有由
v形折叠v形折叠框引发整体
[Music]
there are five configurations of these
结构，然后最后一个和这个
是梦幻般的梦幻童话
there are five configurations of these
folders so I'm going to show you the
我认为这个障碍Ron van der Meer
在这种情况下，这里有
folders so I'm going to show you the
other the other five so this is the type
这是直角V折起
您以这种方式查看平行四边形
other the other five so this is the type
we've just made this is the right angle
当页面关闭时
平行四边形举起你看它
we've just made this is the right angle
v-folds the angles on the pop-up are
直接就可以看到这是
这个平行四边形是建立的
v-folds the angles on the pop-up are
both 90 degrees this is the acute angle
进入这是下一个厨房
内置于其中的是沟渠
both 90 degrees this is the acute angle
v-fold the angles on the pop-up they're
下一个是内置的
本教程就是这样
v-fold the angles on the pop-up they're
still both the same but the angles are
如果你想遵循这是我的
书籍弹出式设计和纸张力学
still both the same but the angles are
both less than 90 degrees this one is
我们看过的一切
他们在这本书中
both less than 90 degrees this one is
the pointy v-folds this is a variation
[音乐]
[掌声]
the pointy v-folds this is a variation
on this acute angle but in this case
[音乐]
您
on this acute angle but in this case
even more extreme this is the this is